Guide to the International Association for Cultural Freedom Records 1941-1978
University of Chicago Library
- Series VI: Latin American Institute of International Relations (ILARI), 1954-1972
  - Subseries 2: Manuscripts
    - Economics Department, Universidad Nacional de Rosario: Trabajo de Investigacion, 1971, N. 18: Luis Albanesi, "Problemas de la elaboración y applicación del Balance intersectorial...," 1971 N. 19: Ricardo Murua, "Modelos para el análisis de los beneficios y pérdidas de la creación dedinero," 1971 N. 20: Tulio A. Ceconi, "Algunas consideraciones sobre el Producto Bruto Interno argentino durante el periodo 1945-1970," 1971 N. 21: Roberto Fattal Jael and Esmeralda Serrato, "La Demanda de Lacteos en la República Argentina," 1971 N. 22: Esmeralda Serrato, "Caracteristicas técnicas de la producción láctea en la Cuenca Santafesina Central," 1971 N. 23: Ricard Murua, "Analisis micro-économico de la actividad bancaria," 1971 N. 24: Estela Valero de Lamanna, "Estudios sobre población," 1971 N. 25: María Noélsida Novo, "Problemas de la planificación financier," 1971 (Box 570, Folder 22)
    - Economics Department, Universidad Nacional de Rosario: Trabajo de Investigacion, 1971-1972, N. 26: Sergio R. Di Pietro, "Formación de precios en una economía socialista," 1971 N. 27: Tulio A. Ceconi, "Metodología para el análisis economico de una region," 1971 N. 28: Juan Luis Morla, Estimacion de las propuestas de inversión de capital ex tranjero autorizadas por Decreto-1959/70," 1971 N. 29: Roberto Fattal Jaef, "Características estructurales de la industria láctea en la Cuenca santafesina Central," 1971 N. 30: Roque Caggiano, "Evolución de la estructura industrial de la Economía Argentina," 1971 N. 32: Francis Dillingham, "Comparaciones entre los sistemas tribtarios de la Argentina y de los Estados Unidos, 1965-1969," 1972 (Box 570, Folder 23)
    - Economics Department, Universidad de Rosario, Resume of Activities, 1972 (Box 570, Folder 24)
    - Conference on Students and Politics, 1967, Memoranda and Agenda, undated Albórnoz, Orlando, "Student Political Activism in Venezuela," 1967 Altbach, Edith H., "Students in the Revolution of 1848," 1967 Altbach, Philip G, "Students and Politics in India," 1967 (Box 571, Folder 1)
    - Conference on Students and Politics, 1967, Bachtiar, Harsja W., "Indonesian Students and their Political Activities," 1967 Bakke, E. Wright, "Mass Demonstrations," 1967 Cornell, Richard, "Students and Politics in the Communist Countries of Eastern Europe," 1967 (Box 571, Folder 2)
    - Conference on Students and Politics, 1967, Finlay, David J., "Students and Politics: The University of Ghana," 1967 Hanna William John and Judith Lynn, "Notes on Political Practices and Perspectives of University of Ibadan and Makerere University College Students," 1967 (Box 571, Folder 3)
    - Conference on Students and Politics, 1967, Hegarty, Thomas J., "Student Movements at Russian Universities," 1967 Hun Oh, Byung, "University Students and Politics in Korea," 1967 (Box 571, Folder 4)
    - Conference on Students and Politics, 1967, Israel, John, "Reflections on the Modern Chinese Student Movement," 1967 Rooks, Charles S., "University Students and Politics in Nigeria," 1967 Shimbori, Michiya, "The Sociology of the Student Movement--a Japanese Case Study," 1967 (Box 571, Folder 5)
    - Conference on Students and Politics, 1967, Silverstein, Josef. "Burmese Student Politics in a Changing Society," 1967 Tomasson, Richard F., "Student Politics and Higher Education in Scandinavia," 1967 Walter, Richard J., "University Reform and Student Politics in Argentina and Peru, 1918-1931," 1967 (Box 571, Folder 6)
    - Special Program of Social Studies in Latin America, "Bibliografia para el estudio de las migraciones," 1970 (Box 572, Folder 1)
    - Special Program of Social Studies in Latin America, "Universidad y estudiantes, bibliografia," 1971 (Box 572, Folder 2)
    - Special Program of Social Studies in Latin America, Contreras, Jaime Castro. "La universida Peruana," 1971 (Box 572, Folder 3)
    - Special Program of Social Studies in Latin America, Contreras, Jaime Castro. "La universida Peruana," 1971 (Box 572, Folder 4)
    - Special Program of Social Studies in Latin America, Zarate, T. "Bibliografia sobre los estudios sociales en el Paraguay," 1971 (Box 572, Folder 5)
    - Special Program of Social Studies in Latin America, "Bases para el studio de las migraciones en America Latina," 1971 (Box 572, Folder 6)
    - Special Program of Social Studies in Latin America, Carlos Banales G. "Funcion politica de las fuerzas armadas Uruguayas," undated (Box 572, Folder 7)
    - Special Program of Social Studies in Latin America, "Proyecto de studio comparative da las universidades en America Latina," undated (Box 572, Folder 8)
    - Military, Beltran, Virgilio, "El estudo de los estuios de sociologia militar en America Latina," undated (Box 572, Folder 9)
    - Military, Cirias, Alberto, "Cuatro ejamplos de relaciones entre fuerzas armadas y poder politico en America Latina," undated (Box 572, Folder 10)
    - Military, Cuéllar, Oscar, "Notas sobre la Participación politica de los militares en America Latina," undated (Box 572, Folder 11)
    - Military, Cullinan, Terrence, "Servicio Nacional en vez del Militar?" undated (Box 572, Folder 12)
    - Unidentified Pages, undated (Box 572, Folder 13)
    - Activity Reports, 1965-1969 (Box 572, Folder 14)
  - Subseries 3: Reports and Projects
    - Activity Reports, 1968-1971 (Box 573, Folder 1)
    - Activities Reports, 1970-1971 (Box 573, Folder 2)
    - Summary of Major Activities, 1965-1966 (Box 573, Folder 3)
    - ADELA Investment Company, 1968 (Box 573, Folder 4)
    - ADELA Investment Company, Monthly Bulletins, 1969-1972 (Box 573, Folder 5)
    - Aportes, 1968-1972 (Box 573, Folder 6)
    - Argentina, 1966 (Box 573, Folder 7)
    - Argentine Center for Cultural Freedom, clippings and photographs, 1965-1966, Theater Conference Antonio Berni dialogue with Edward Gonzale Lanuza Polemic Dialogues "Third World" Collection (Box 573, Folder 8)
    - Argentine Center for Cultural Freedom, clippings and photographs, 1966, Humanist Library Inauguration Pierre Emmanuel visit to Buenos Aires Leopoldo Marechal debate Afranio Coutinho visit to Buenos Aires Conference on Audiovisual Means in Contemporary Communication (Box 573, Folder 9)
    - Argentine Center for Cultural Freedom, clippings and photographs, 1966, Carlos Archiiacono Albert Espada José Luis Macchione Eduardo B. Levy (Box 573, Folder 10)
    - Argentine Center for Cultural Freedom, clippings and photographs, 1966, Alcides Gubellini Carlos H. Zárate Group of Integration for Simultaneous Action (Box 573, Folder 11)
    - Argentine Center for Cultural Freedom, clippings and photographs, 1967, "The Writer Speaks With His Public: Haroldo Conti" Conference on the course of Contemporary Philosophy by Eduardo Rabossi H. A. Murena visit to Bogotá Review of Records Published by the Argentine Center (Box 573, Folder 12)
    - Argentine Center for Cultural Freedom, clippings and photographs, 1967, Carlos Uria Five Engravers Claudio Rodriques Ponce Nicolas Rubio Critique of Ideal Sanchez (Box 573, Folder 13)
    - Argentine Center for Cultural Freedom, clippings and photographs, 1967-1968, José Manuel Moraña Orion Group Surrealism Cristina Santander. (Box 573, Folder 14)
    - Banco Interamericano de Desarrollo, 1969-1972 (Box 573, Folder 15)
    - Boletin IIEE, 1972 (Box 574, Folder 1)
    - Bolivia, 1966 (Box 574, Folder 2)
    - Brazil, 1961-1962 (Box 574, Folder 3)
    - Chile, 1966 (Box 574, Folder 4)
    - Directory of the Activities of the Gallery of Culture and Freedom,1969 (Box 574, Folder 5)
    - Dominican Republic, 1961-1962 (Box 574, Folder 6)
    - ICIA, 1972 (Box 574, Folder 7)
    - ILARI, Organizational Conference, 1965 (Box 574, Folder 8)
    - ILARI, Statutes, undated (Box 574, Folder 9)
    - ILARI, Functions and Programs, undated (Box 574, Folder 10)
    - ILARI Third Reunion, 1966 (Box 574, Folder 11)
    - ILARI Fourth Reunion, 1969 (Box 574, Folder 12)
    - Reports on ILARI, 1967 (Box 574, Folder 13)
    - Reports on ILARI, 1969 (Box 574, Folder 14)
    - Indicadores Economicos, 1971 (Box 574, Folder 15)
    - Memoranda, 1965-1966 (Box 574, Folder 16)
    - Memoranda, 1965-1966 (Box 574, Folder 17)
    - Memoranda, 1968 (Box 574, Folder 18)
    - Mundo Nuevo, 1968-1969 (Box 574, Folder 19)
    - Notas sobre la economia y el desarrollo de América Latina, 1972 (Box 574, Folder 20)
    - Noticiario Obrero Interamericano, 1972 (Box 574, Folder 21)
    - Paraguay, 1961-1966 (Box 574, Folder 22)
    - Paris Meeting, 1966 (Box 574, Folder 23)
    - Peru, 1972 (Box 574, Folder 24)
    - Projects, Memoranda, Press Releases, 1966-1967 (Box 574, Folder 25)
    - Projects, 1966 (Box 574, Folder 26)
    - Projects, undated (Box 574, Folder 27)
    - Program Proposal, "The Crisis of Rationality", 1967 (Box 574, Folder 28)
    - Report on the Bonn Seminar, 1972 (Box 574, Folder 29)
    - Report on Internal Migrations in Latin America, 1968 (Box 574, Folder 30)
    - Report on Latin American Economic Integration, 1964 (Box 574, Folder 31)
    - Report on Luis Mercier Vega's trip to Latin America, 1961 (Box 574, Folder 32)
    - Report on Luis Mercier Vega's trip to Latin America, 1967 (Box 574, Folder 33)
    - Report on trip to Ecuador, Peru and Chile, undated (Box 574, Folder 34)
    - Trip Reports, 1965-1966 (Box 575, Folder 1)
    - Reports, Book Mailing Lists, 1970-1972 (Box 575, Folder 2)
    - Reports, Journals, Radio Scripts, 1966-1971 (Box 575, Folder 3)
    - Reports, Press Clipping Service, 1965-1966 (Box 575, Folder 4)
    - Reports, Projects, Memoranda, 1961-1963 (Box 575, Folder 5)
    - Reports, Projects, Memoranda, 1964-1966 (Box 575, Folder 6)
    - Reports, Projects, Memoranda, 1967 (Box 575, Folder 7)
    - Reports, Projects, Memoranda, 1968-1969 (Box 575, Folder 8)
    - Reports, Projects, Memoranda, 1970 (Box 575, Folder 9)
    - Reports, Projects, Memoranda, 1970-1971 (Box 575, Folder 10)
    - Reports, Résumés, Addresses, 1966 (Box 575, Folder 11)
    - Reports, Seminars and Projects, Miscellaneous, 1964-1967 (Box 575, Folder 12)
    - Reports, Questionnaires, undated (Box 575, Folder 13)
    - SIC, 1972 (Box 575, Folder 14)
    - Uruguay, 1966-1968 (Box 575, Folder 15)
    - Venezuela, 1966 (Box 575, Folder 16)
  - Subseries 4: Financial Records
    - Aportes, Distribution, 1966-1972 (Box 576, Folder 1)
    - Argentina, 1964-1971 (Box 576, Folder 2)
    - Bolivia, 1965-1970 (Box 576, Folder 3)
    - Brazil, 1964-1967 (Box 576, Folder 4)
    - Brazil, 1968-1970 (Box 576, Folder 5)
    - Budgets; London IACF Comptroller, 1964-1965 (Box 576, Folder 6)
    - Budgets; Comptroller Correspondence; Aportes; Trabajos, 1966 (Box 576, Folder 7)
    - Budgets; Comptroller Correspondence; Paris; Aportes; Trabajos, 1967 (Box 576, Folder 8)
    - Budgets; Paris; Aportes, 1968 (Box 576, Folder 9)
    - Publications: Aportes; Mundo Nuevo; Trabajos, 1968 (Box 576, Folder 10)
    - Budgets; Paris; Aportes; Trabajos, 1969 (Box 577, Folder 1)
    - Budgets; Paris; Publications, 1970 (Box 577, Folder 2)
    - Budgets; Latin American Centers; Paris; Publications, 1971 (Box 577, Folder 3)
    - Publications: Aportes, 1971 (Box 577, Folder 4)
    - Paris; Aportes, 1972 (Box 577, Folder 5)
    - Chile, 1966 (Box 577, Folder 6)
    - Colombia, 1968 (Box 577, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, General, 1967-1971 (Box 577, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, Homero Alsina Thevenet, 1966-1968 (Box 577, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, Department Etranger Hachette, 1972 (Box 577, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, Memoranda and Shipments to Authors, 1972 (Box 577, Folder 11)
    - Cuadernos, Subscription Correspondence, 1959 (Box 577, Folder 12)
    - ILARI Reunion, 1967 (Box 577, Folder 13)
    - Mexico, 1965-1966 (Box 577, Folder 14)
    - Mundo Nuevo, Distribution, 1966-1969 (Box 578, Folder 1)
    - Mundo Nuevo, Distribution, 1969-1970 (Box 578, Folder 2)
    - Mundo Nuevo, Exchanges, 1966-1968 (Box 578, Folder 3)
    - Mundo Nuevo, Exchanges, 1966-1969 (Box 578, Folder 4)
    - Mundo Nuevo, Payments to Contributors, 1966-1968 (Box 578, Folder 5)
    - Mundo Nuevo, Payments to Contributors, 1966-1968 (Box 578, Folder 6)
    - Mundo Nuevo, Payments to Contributors, 1969-1971 (Box 578, Folder 7)
    - Mundo Nuevo, Subscription Correspondence, 1964-1969 (Box 578, Folder 8)
    - Mundo Nuevo, Subscription Correspondence, 1964-1970 (Box 579, Folder 1)
    - Mundo Nuevo, Subscription Correspondence, 1967-1971 (Box 579, Folder 2)
    - Mundo Nuevo, Subscription Lists, 1966-1970 (Box 579, Folder 3)
    - Paraguay, 1965-171 (Box 579, Folder 4)
    - Peru, 1965-1971 (Box 579, Folder 5)
    - Remittance of Checks, 1966-1971 (Box 579, Folder 6)
    - Serial distribution: Argentina, Brazil, 1966-1970 (Box 579, Folder 7)
    - Serial distribution: Canary Islands, Dominican Republic, Ecuador, France, Guatemala, Honduras, Italy, 1966-1970 (Box 580, Folder 1)
    - Serial distribution: Mexico, 1966-1971 (Box 580, Folder 2)
    - Serial distribution: Mexico, 1966-1972 (Box 580, Folder 3)
    - Serial distribution: Panama, Paraguay, Peru, 1964-1970 (Box 580, Folder 4)
    - Serial distribution: Puerto Rico, Uruguay, USA, 1964-1970 (Box 580, Folder 5)
    - Uruguay, 1964-1970 (Box 580, Folder 6)
    - Venezuela, 1967 (Box 580, Folder 7)
- Series VII: Preuves Papers
  Preuves, a journal sponsored by the CCF which appeared monthly between 1951 and 1959, had a closer relationship to the CCF than other sponsored journals because it was published in Paris, the Congress' headquarters. Its editorial policy was characterized by three areas of special interest: European intellectuals in relation to emergent European community; the situation and problems of intellectuals in communist states; and colonial wars and the consequences of decolonization.
  The Preuves papers consist primarily of correspondence, although they also include a substantial section of manuscript material. The correspondence is arranged alphabetically by subject with folders containing other material so designated, e.g., distribution statistics, newsletters, memoranda, etc. The original order was preserved where possible; hence, some correspondence is arranged alphabetically and some chronologically.
  Major correspondents include the Editorial Committee, consisting of François Bondy (political and literary director of Preuves, as well as director of publications for the Congress), Jean Bloch-Michel (literary editor and director-general of Censure, another CCF publication), and Jacques Carat (editor-in-chief and general administrator). Extensive correspondence of Louis Mercier Vega, editorial secretary, is also included. The Preuves papers also contain records of affiliate organizations such as "Amis de Preuves" (a book club), "Amis de la Liberté" (the French CCF group whose name was changed in the 1960's to "Cercles Pour la Liberté de la Culture") and the "Mardis de Preuves" (a Tuesday night debate society). These groups comprised a support network for the journal, contributing financial aid beyond revenues derived from subscriptions.
  All manuscripts are arranged alphabetically by author's last name, preserving the original order of a major block of manuscripts. However, some manuscripts were originally ordered by the issue in which they appeared. These groups of manuscripts were broken up and integrated into the alphabetical sequence. Titles of manuscripts where listed indicate the presence of two or more manuscripts by a single author. Corrected galley proofs are filed with the author's manuscripts.
  - Subseries 1: Administration and General Correspondence
    - Administration, Encounter, 1953-1963 (Box 581, Folder 1)
    - Administration, Encounter, 1961-1966 (Box 581, Folder 2)
    - Administration, General, 1952 (Box 581, Folder 3)
    - Administration, General, 1952-1955 (Box 581, Folder 4)
    - Administration, General, Financial, 1960-1962 (Box 581, Folder 5)
    - Administration, Librairie Hachette, 1953-1963 (Box 581, Folder 6)
    - Administration, Librairie Hachette, 1964-1969 (Box 581, Folder 7)
    - Administration, General, 1966 (Box 581, Folder 8)
    - Administration, Mazarakis, 1953-1964 (Box 581, Folder 9)
    - Administration, Memoranda, 1956-September 1959 (Box 582, Folder 1)
    - Administration, Memoranda, October 1959-March 1960 (Box 582, Folder 2)
    - Administration, Memoranda, April 1960-December 1960 (Box 582, Folder 3)
    - Administration, Memoranda, 1961 (Box 582, Folder 4)
    - Administration, Memoranda, 1961 (Box 582, Folder 5)
    - Administration, Memoranda, 1961-1962 (Box 582, Folder 6)
    - Administration, Memoranda, 1962-1963 (Box 583, Folder 1)
    - Administration, Memoranda, 1963-1964 (Box 583, Folder 2)
    - Administration, Memoranda, 1964-1965 (Box 583, Folder 3)
    - Administration, Memoranda, 1966-1969 (Box 583, Folder 4)
    - Administration, N.M.P.P. (Nouvelle Messagerie de la Presse Parisienne), 1963-1969 (Box 583, Folder 5)
    - Administration, Subscriptions, 1966 (Box 583, Folder 6)
    - Biographical sketches of Preuves authors, 1953-1966 (Box 583, Folder 7)
    - Budgets, 1959-1969 (Box 584, Folder 1)
    - Complimentary copies, 1951-1965 (Box 584, Folder 2)
    - Complimentary copies, 1962-1966 (Box 584, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence with Congress Business Manager, R. Farrand, 1962-1963 (Box 584, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence with Congress Business Manager, R. Farrand, 1963-1964 (Box 584, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence with Congress Business Manager, 1962-1969 (Box 584, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, Leontyne Price, 1952-1956 (Box 584, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, Argentina-Belgium, 1952-1968, Argentina, 1956-1968 Australia, 1953-1960 Belgium, 1952-1959 (Box 584, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, Brazil-Chile, 1951-1969, Brazil, 1953-1967 Bulgaria, 1954-1959 Canada, 1953-1956 Chile, 1951-1969 (Box 585, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, Congo-Ecuador, 1953-1969, Congo, 1954-1969 Costa Rica, 1953-1957 Cuba, 1953-1967 Czechoslovakia, 1956 Denmark, 1959-1962 Ecuador, 1955-1966 (Box 585, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, Egypt-England, 1953-1962, Egypt, 1953-1962 England, 1962 (Box 585, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, France, 1959 (Box 585, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, Greece-Italy, 1954-1966, Greece, 1958-1963 Italy, 1954-1966 (Box 585, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, Japan-Laos, 1953-1966, Japan, 1953-1966 Jordan, 1954 Katanga, 1962 Laos, 1959-1963 (Box 585, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, Lebanon, 1954-1969 (Box 585, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, Libya-Malaya, 1953-1966, Libya, 1959 Luxembourg, 1953-1965 Latin America, 1966 Malaya, 1963-1966 (Box 586, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, Morocco, 1954-1969 (Box 586, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, Mexico-South Vietnam, 1951-1969, Mexico, 1953-1962 Poland, 1951-1956 Portugal, 1951-1963 Rumania, 1952-1969 South Vietnam, 1956-1961 (Box 586, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, Andorra, Spain, A-K, 1953-1969 (Box 586, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, Spain, L-Z, 1953-1969 (Box 586, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, Switzerland-Syria, 1953-1965, Switzerland, 1953-1965 Syria, 1962 (Box 586, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, United States, 1957-1968 (Box 587, Folder 1)
    - Distribution Statistics, 1951-1955 (Box 587, Folder 2)
    - Distribution Statistics, 1956-1961 (Box 587, Folder 3)
    - Distribution statistics, 1962-1967 Folder 5: Distribution statistics, 1952-1962 (Box 587, Folder 4)
    - Distribution statistics, 1955-1962 (Box 587, Folder 6)
    - Distribution statistics, 1955-1962 (Box 587, Folder 7)
    - Distribution statistics, 1957-1964 (Box 588, Folder 1)
    - Distribution statistics, 1959 (Box 588, Folder 2)
    - Distribution statistics, 1960-1964 (Box 588, Folder 3)
    - Distribution statistics, 1962-1964 (Box 588, Folder 4)
    - Individual Subscriptions, Complimentary letters, 1954-1958 (Box 588, Folder 5)
    - Individual Subscriptions, 1959-1966 (Box 588, Folder 6)
    - Individual subscriptions, Subscription statistics, 1955-1969 (Box 588, Folder 7)
    - Miscellaneous, 1962 (Box 588, Folder 8)
    - Network of contacts, 1951-1966 (Box 589, Folder 1)
    - Potential subscribers, Individuals and Institutions, 1951-1967 (Box 589, Folder 2)
    - Potential subscribers, Individuals and Institutions, 1951-1968 (Box 589, Folder 3)
    - Press Releases, Issues 12-136, 1952-1962 (Box 589, Folder 4)
    - Press Releases, Issues 137-220, 1962-1969 (Box 589, Folder 5)
    - Renewals and Requests, Subscription Terminations, 1952-1969 (Box 589, Folder 6)
    - Reports to the Government, Postal Regulations, 1953-1968 (Box 589, Folder 7)
    - Testimonials, Promotional Bilingual Issue, 1954-1963 (Box 590, Folder 1)
  - Subseries 2: Concours de Citations
    - Concours de Citations (Competition of quotes), A-H, 1960-1969 (Box 590, Folder 2)
    - Concours de Citations (Competition of quotes), I-T, 1960-1969 (Box 590, Folder 3)
    - Concours de Citations (Competition of quotes), V-Z, 1961-1969 (Box 590, Folder 4)
  - Subseries 3: Congress for Cultural Freedom
    - Address lists, 1962-1965, Bulletin du Congrès Bulletin de Censure Cercles pour la Liberté de la Culture Commission Internationale pour la Verité sur les Crimes de Stalin France-Algeria, Association (Box 590, Folder 5)
    - Address lists, 1964-1965, Mardi de Preuves Press (Box 590, Folder 6)
    - Address lists, Union des Ecrivains pour la Verité, 1962-1965 (Box 590, Folder 7)
    - Distribution of Publications, A-B, 1954-1956 (Box 590, Folder 8)
    - Distribution of Publications, C-D, 1955-1956 (Box 591, Folder 1)
    - Distribution of Publications, E, 1955-1957 (Box 591, Folder 2)
    - Distribution of Publications, F-H, 1955-1956 (Box 591, Folder 3)
    - Distribution of Publications, I-L, 1955-1956 (Box 591, Folder 4)
    - Distribution of Publications, M-O, 1954-1957 (Box 591, Folder 5)
    - Distribution of Publications, P-R, 1955-1956 (Box 591, Folder 6)
    - Distribution of Publications, S, 1954-1957 (Box 592, Folder 1)
    - Distribution of Publications, T-W, 1955-1956 (Box 592, Folder 2)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, 1954-1955 (Box 592, Folder 3)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, 1955-1956 (Box 592, Folder 4)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, 1956-1957 (Box 592, Folder 5)
    - Prospective subscribers, 1955-1956 (Box 592, Folder 6)
    - Reorganization, 1967-1969 (Box 592, Folder 7)
    - Steimatzky’s Agency (Israel), 1956-1958 (Box 593, Folder 1)
  - Subseries 4: Contributors to the Financial Support of Preuves
    - Correspondence, A-Be, 1963-1969 (Box 593, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, Bi-Br, 1963-1969 (Box 593, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, C-D, 1963-1969 (Box 593, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, E-F, 1963-1969 (Box 593, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, G-H, 1963-1969 (Box 593, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, I-K, 1963-1969 (Box 594, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, L, 1963-1969 (Box 594, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, M, 1963-1969 (Box 594, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, N-O, 1963-1969 (Box 594, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, P, 1963-1969 (Box 594, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, Q-R, 1963-1969 (Box 594, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, S, 1963-1969 (Box 594, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, T-Z, 1963-1969 (Box 595, Folder 1)
    - Form letters on special issues, publicity and subscription prices, 1951-1968 (Box 595, Folder 2)
    - Form letters on subscriptions, 1955-1968 (Box 595, Folder 3)
    - Form letters on price changes, 1959-1969 (Box 595, Folder 4)
    - French Newspapermen's Unions, 1963 (Box 595, Folder 5)
    - Invitations, Cocktails, Receptions, 1960 (Box 595, Folder 6)
  - Subseries 5: Printers
    - Imprimerie Réaumer; Imprimerie de Clichy; Imprimerie de la S.N.E.P., 1951-1959 (Box 595, Folder 7)
    - Imprimerie Firmin-Didot, 1952-1969 (Box 595, Folder 8)
    - Public relations, 1952-1960 (Box 595, Folder 9)